Hey there, I wanted to take a second at the end of it all, at the end of your learning journey
to just say this one thing and that is thank you. I know your time is valuable. We have limited time
on this earth and you decided to spend your time and your money frankly with us doing something
that takes a long time to learn. So truly from the bottom of our hearts I know it sounds cheesy
but thank you for dedicating your time and effort to this course. I hope you got what you wanted out
of it and congratulate yourself for getting this far because a lot of people start, a lot of people
have hopes of learning but they give up along the way. But you didn't do that. You worked through
the challenges, the problems and you got here. Now your learning journey doesn't end here. It keeps
going but I hope this created a foundation for you to go off and learn things on your own. Get
a promotion, get hired, start a new business. Whatever it may be, again thank you and best of
luck with your learning journey. This is just the beginning of whatever you decide to do in the future.
So thank you and good luck.