Welcome back. So in the last video we covered briefly the difference between
traditional programming and machine learning and again I don't want to spend
too much time on definitions. I'd rather you see this in practice. And I left you
with the question, why would you want to use machine learning or deep learning?
Well let's think of a good reason. Why not? I mean if we had to write all those
handwritten rules to reproduce Alcison and Grandmother's roast chicken dish all
the time that would be quite cumbersome right? Well let's draw a line on that. Why
not? What's a better reason? Kind of what we just said right? For a complex problem
can you think of all the rules? So let's imagine we're trying to build a self
driving car. Now if you've learned to drive you've probably done so in maybe
20 hours, 100 hours, but now I'll give you a task of writing down every single
rule about driving. How do you back out of your driveway? How do you turn left
and go down the street? How do you park a reverse park? How do you stop at an
intersection? How do you know how fast to go somewhere? So we just listed half a
dozen rules but you could probably go a fair few more. You might get into the
thousands. And so for a complex problem such as driving can you think of all the
rules? Well probably not. So that's where machine learning and deep learning come
into help. And so this is a beautiful comment I like to share with you on one
of my YouTube videos is my 2020 machine learning roadmap and this is from
Yashui. I'm probably going to mispronounce this if I even try to. But
Yashui says I think you can use ML. So ML is machine learning. I'm going to use
that a lot throughout the course by the way. ML is machine learning just so you
know. For literally anything as long as you can convert it into numbers. Ah
that's what we said before machine learning is turning something into
computer readable numbers and then programming it to find patterns except
with a machine learning algorithm typically we write the algorithm and it
finds the patterns not us. And so literally it could be anything any input
or output from the universe. That's pretty darn cool about machine learning
right? But should you always use it just because it could be used for anything?
Well I'd like to also introduce you to Google's number one rule of machine
learning. Now if you can build a simple rule
based system such as the step of five rules that we had to map the ingredients
to our Sicilian grandmother's roast chicken dish. If you can write just five
steps to do that that's going to work every time. Well you should probably do
that. So if you can build a simple rule based system that doesn't require machine
learning do that. And of course maybe it's not so very simple but maybe you
can just write some rules to solve the problem that you're working on. Now this
is from a wise software engineer which is I kind of hinted at it before. Rule one
of Google's machine learning handbook. Now I'm going to highly recommend you
read through that but we're not going to go through that in this video so check
that out you can Google that otherwise the links will be where you get links. So
just keep that in mind although machine learning is very powerful and very fun
and very excited it doesn't mean that you should always use it. I know this is
quite the thing to be saying at the start of a deep learning and machine
learning course but I just want you to keep in mind simple rule based systems
are still good. Machine learning isn't a solve-all for everything. Now let's have
a look at what deep learning is good for but I'm going to leave you on a
cliffhanger because we're going to check this out in the next video. See you soon.